你们知道
Robin阿姨是个万圣节迷
Now, as you know, aunt robin is a big fan of halloween
每次都装扮的很疯狂
always dressing up in crazy costumes
但是她以前并不是那样
but she wasn't always that way.
回溯到2005年
她认为万圣节太幼稚了
Back in 2005,she thought she was too cool for halloween,
不象Lily阿姨
unlike aunt lily.
猜今天有什么东西寄过来了?
Guess what came in the mail today?
我们的服装吗?
Our costumes?
-够劲爆吗？
-够劲爆
-Do they rule? -They rule.
你的是100%羊毛的
这次不会象去年那样体温过高了
And yours is 100% wool,so you won't get hypothermia like last year.
泰山的蓝乳头
Tarzan nipples blue.
你们知道我最喜欢
万圣节的什么吗?
You know what I love about halloween?
这是个女人们释放内心欲望的夜晚
It's the one night of the year chicks use to unleash their inner ho-bag.
如果一个女生装扮成女巫
那么她就是个放浪的女巫
If a girl dresses up as a witch,she's a slutty witch.
如果她装扮成一只猫
她就是一只放浪的猫
If she's a cat,she's a slutty cat.
如果她装扮成护士...
If she's a nurse...
我们知道了
w,we get it.
... 她就是个放浪的护士
...She's a slutty nurse.
Robin, 万圣节你打算干嘛?
Robin,what are you doing for halloween?
噢, 我也不知道
Oh,I don't know.
可能跟Mike一起过
这家伙和我在约会
Probably hanging out with mike,this guy've been seeing.
Mike? 有个Mike吗? 你有男朋友了
而你却没告诉我们?
Mike? There's a mike? You have a boyfriend
and you haven't told us?
不, 我是说, 他不是我男朋友
只是这几周和我约会的家伙
No,I mean,he's not my boyfriend. He's just this guy
I've been seeing for a couple of weeks.
- 男朋友!
- 那为什么我们没见过他?
-Boyfriend! -So why haven't we met him?
我们还没准备好公开
We're not really ready to go public yet.
结婚啦
Married.
万圣节我们来个4人约会怎么样?
How about we go on a halloween double date?
我不知道, 我们在考虑
是不是呆在家装扮成裸体人
I don't know,we were kind of thinking
about staying at home and dressing up as naked people.
拜托, Robin, 炫耀下你的新男友
Come on,robin,trot out your new fella.
让我们有机会在你背后
评论他 这很好玩
Let us judge and evaluate him behind your back. It'll be fun.
嘿, Ted, 你肯定猜不到发生什么了
Hey,ted,you'll never guess what happened.
- 你们的服装寄过来了?
- 我们的服...
-Your costumes came? Our cost...
是啊 这就是为什么
我们是最好的朋友
-yes. That is why we're best friends.
- 嘿, Ted, 万圣节打算怎么过?
- 嗯...
-Hey,ted,what are you doing for halloween?
-Well...
怎么?
what?
每次万圣节, Ted都
在等那个放浪的南瓜
Every halloween,ted waits for the slutty pumpkin.
正确
That's right.
"放浪的南瓜"是什么东西?
What's the "slutty pumpkin"?
你应该说谁是放浪的南瓜
那是4年前...
You mean who is the slutty pumpkin.
It was four years ago...
就在我们楼顶的万圣节派对上
I was at this halloween party up on the roof of our building.
在傍晚的时候不知从哪里
这个穿着性感南瓜装的女孩出现了
I'm about to call it an early night when out of nowhere appeared this girl in the sexiest pumpkin costume.
等等, 南瓜装怎么个性感法?
Wait,how can a pumpkin costume be sexy?
关键性的部位都挖空了
It was carved in strategic places.
后来, 呃, 我们去了吧台
我见识到了她的混合咖啡酒
So,uh,we're at the bar,and I see her mix kahlua.
她自己发明调制的鸡尾酒
A cocktail she invented herself.
她把它叫做... "巧克力糖"
And she called it... "the tootsie roll..."
因为它尝起来象
酒味儿十足的巧克力糖
Because it tastes like an alcoholic tootsie roll.
嘿! 我能自己讲这个吗?
Hey! Can I please tell the story?
我们间来了点感觉
So we had this instant connection.
她给了我电话, 但是后来...
She gave me her number,but then...
发生了件很恐怖的事情
Something went terribly wrong.
伙计们!
Guys!
发生了件很恐怖的事情
Then something went terribly wrong.
万圣节快乐
Happy halloween.
Sonny, Cher在哪儿?
Sonny,where's cher?
- Cher?
- 来啦, 宝贝
-Cher?
-Right here,babe.
我刚碰见了个完美的女人
I just met the perfect woman.
她很风趣, 很漂亮，喜欢看星球大战
She's funny,she's beautiful,she loves star wars.
哇, 哇, 她对伊娃族的看法呢?
Whoa,whoa,whoa,whoa,what's her take on ewoks?
- 很喜欢 - 噢, 太好了
-Loves 'em. -Oh,good.
我不明白为什么人们这么讨厌伊娃族
如果没有伊娃族反叛者就会输掉
I don't know why people are so cynical about ewoks.
The rebellion would have failed without the ewoks.
还有: 她是海洋生物学家
她花了一年在南极研究企鹅
And get this: She's a marine biologist.
She spent a year in antarctica studying penguins.
噢, 企鹅真酷
就象黑白的伊娃族
Oh,penguins are cool. Kind of like black and white ewoks.
我同意
I approve.
嘿, 我的, 呃, 巧克力糖在哪?
我就放在这桌上了
Hey,where's my,uh,kit-kat? I put it right here on this table.
我不知道
但这里有很多巧克力
I don't know,but we've plenty of chocolate here.
不, 不, 你不明白
我需要那个巧克力糖
No,no,you don't understand.
I need that kit-kat
她把电话写在那个包装纸上了 在哪?
she wrote her number on that wrapper. Where is it?
嘿, ... 吸血鬼!
Hey,dracula!
拜托, 给我... 把它给我!
Come on,give me the... give me it!
巧克力糖在哪?
巧克力糖在哪?!
Where's the kit-kat?
Where's the kit-kat?!
再也找不到她的电话号码了
Never found her number
再也没见过她了
never saw her again.
但是每年他们都在楼顶办派对
那就是我要去的地方
But every year,they have a halloween party up on the roof,
so that's where I'll be.
你知道, Ted, 已经4年了
You know,ted,it's been four years.
她可能已经订婚或者结婚了
或者, 老天保佑, 变得很胖
She could be engaged or married,or,god forbid,fat.
我不知道, 我有种感觉
I don't know,I got a feeling
就是今年了 万圣节是
一个充满未知和魔法的夜晚
this could be the year. Halloween is a night of wonder and magic.
- 好吧
- 尽管嘲笑, 没事, 我能承受住
-all right.
-bring the mockery,fine,I can take it.
但是拜托, 如果那放浪的南瓜
真是我未来的老婆这不是很酷吗?
But come on,wouldn't it be the coolest story ever
if the slutty pumpkin turned out to be my future wife?
噢, 为了以防万一
我们也许该停止叫她放浪的南瓜
Oh,on the off-chance that that could happen,
maybe we should stop calling her the slutty pumpkin.
- 这提议不错
- 这主意不错
-That's a really good point.
-That's a good idea.
Ted, 你准备好被震撼了吗
震撼, 震撼?
-Ted,is your world ready to be rocked,rock,rocked?
等不及了
-Can't wait.
那么... 你觉得怎么样?
So... what do you think?
那么, 你觉得怎么样?
So,what do you think?
Marshall, 你画眼影了
Marshall,are you wearing eyeliner
噢, 是啊, 另类的性感, 是不?
oh,yeah. Weirdly hot,right?
我们会赢得今年的最佳装扮奖
We are so going to win the costume contest this year.
第一名的奖金, 50元的酒吧消费卷
First prize: $50 gift certificate at the bar.
你们的服装花了多少钱?
And how much did you pay for your costumes?
- 100块
- 一个人
-$100.
-Each.
嗯, 我觉得你们看起来很不错
Well,I think you guys look great.
你要扮成什么? 噢, 我干嘛问
What are you going as? Oh,like I even need to ask.
嘿, 我希望放浪的南瓜认的出我
她见到我的时候我是个...
Hey,I want the slutty pumpkin to recognize me,and she knows me as...
一个投票牌
a hanging chad.
怎么? 她觉得很不错啊
What? She thought it was hilarious.
嗯, 4年前了, 但是没人会记得投票牌是什么
Yeah,four years ago,but nobody remembers
what the hell a hanging chad is.
多可悲的观点啊，我们怎能忘记政治历史上如此动荡的时刻
What a sad commentary on our national attention span that we could forget such a turbulent time in our political history.
可悲的观点
Sad commentary.
好吧, Polly要尿尿了
all right,polly got to pee.
又要?
Again?
你去干什么?
Where you going?
这是套精心制作的制服
It's an elaborate costume.
别, 别, 别又这样, 别今年
你要装扮成我的僚机飞行员，穿上
no,no,not again,not this year. You're going as my wingman. Flight suit up.
不 谢了 我仍着迷我的选举牌
No thanks. I'm sticking with the hanging chad.
噢, 你危险了, 迷途羔羊
Oh,you're dangerous,maverick.
你的身体兑现不了你的自以为是开出的支票
Your ego's writing checks your body can't cash.
好吧
Okay.
现在有个计划，我可以让你改变主意
Here's the plan,and I crap you not.
我能把我们弄进维多利亚的秘密万圣派对
I'm getting us into the victoria's secret halloween party.
相信我, 今晚你的牌子不会挂起来
Trust me,by the end of the night,your chad will not be hanging.
我们能在一年里的任何一晚被那些模特拒绝
We can get rejected by supermodels any night of the year.
今晚我要去楼顶，喝点啤酒, 等着放浪南瓜
Tonight I'm going up to the roof,I'm going to have a few beers,
I'm going to wait for the slutty pumpkin.
这就是我要做的
It's just what I do.
维多利亚秘密派对的模特们在酒吧里狂欢...
Victoria's secret models prancing around in bras and panties...
或者耶鲁预科毕业生的愚蠢卡聚会
or yale preppies reuniting their stupid a capella group.
你说什么, 左手?
"右手真逊"? 说对了
What's that,left hand?
"Right hand sucks"? Word.
我要去楼顶了
Heading up to the roof.
好吧, 伙计们, 看起来就我们3个
Well,boys,looks like it's just the three of us.
什么? "自己击掌"? 好的
我们出去了
What's that? "Self five"?
Nice. We out.
嘿, 投票牌, 挂的怎么样?
Hey,chad,how's it hanging?
嘿, 拼字游戏, 好玩
Hey,word play,funny.
哇 不错的服装
Whoo,nice outfit.
- 我是鹦鹉
- 你当然是
-I'm a parrot.
-You sure are.
Mike在哪? 他会来这找我
Where's mike? He's meeting me here.
村庄里的万圣节游行我去晚了
那里, 就象, 千万个同性恋海盗
I ran late covering the halloween parade in the village.
There are,like,a zillion gay pirates this year.
认真的说, 我的眼影看起来还好吧?
Seriously,does my eyeliner look okay?
对, 另类的性感
Yes,it's weirdly hot.
嗯, 你的服装呢?
So,where's your costume?
呃, 我和Mike想着一起做些什么
最后决定我们都不装扮
uh,you know,mike and I joked about doing something together,
but we decided not to dress up.
噢, 天那
Oh,geez.
呃, 各位, 这是Michael
这不是他的头发
Uh,everyone,this is michael.
That is not his real hair.
呃, 你的服装呢, Gretel?
格林童话《Hansel & Gretel》里的人物
中文译名《糖果屋》
Um,where's your costume,gretel?
你认为我是... 噢, 我是在开玩笑
我得停止在邮件上开玩笑
这样很难传达到我的想法
You thought I was... oh,I was just kidding.
I've got to stop making jokes in e-mails. It's so hard to convey tone.
我想我们肯定打败他们
I think we got them beat.
- 我不敢相信你说服我来这
- 我没有 是你自己跟过来的
-I can't believe you talked me into this.
-I didn't. You followed me up here.
这派对真烂
This party sucks.
只有7个女人
There's seven chicks here.
只有6个了
There's six chicks here.
放松点 夜晚才刚刚开始 会变好的
Relax. The night is young. It's going to get better.
先生们小姐们，仍然和95年见面会时一样
Ladies and gentlemen,as on pitch as they were at spring fling '95,
我荣幸的欢迎Shaggarats
it's my pleasure to welcome back the shaggarats.
海盗最喜欢的是哪类毛线衫?
What be a pirate's favorite kind of sweater?
Arr-gyle
Arr-gyle.
海盗最喜欢的快餐店是哪家?
And what be a pirate's favorite fast food restaurant?
Arr-by's
Arr-by'S.
你可能觉得是Arby's（美国知名三明治快餐店）
You would think it would be arby's.
但是, 事实上, 是Long John Silver's
美国另一知名快餐店
But,actually,it's long john silver'S.
事实上, 我需要这只手来吃饭 噢...
actually,I kind of need this hand to eat. Oh..
很高兴见到你, Mike 你们在一起太配了
It's so nice to meet you,mike. You guys are really cute together.
对啊, 我们在一起渡过了很多时光
我们甚至分享对方的...
Yeah,we've been spending a lot of time together.
We're even getting to that point where we finish each other'S.
...这汉堡太... 棒了 看?
.. this cheeseburger is so... good. See?
我觉得你该赢得今晚的免费卷, 宝贝
I think you won the dish-off tonight,baby.
这牛排打败了我的猪排
This steak totally bitch-slapped my pork chops.
可能是真的,但是如果吃了一点你的肉饭我的菠菜就可以被踢走了
That may be true,but your rice pilaf kicked my spinach in the crotch so hard it threw up a little bit.
Robin, 你得尝尝这鸡肉
Robin,you have to try this chicken.
噢, 没事, 我很好, 谢谢
Oh,that's good,I'm okay,thanks.
- 这真的很好吃
- 我正在品尝这个汉堡
-It's really tasty.
-I'm just really feeling this cheeseburger.
来吧, 只尝一点就好了
Come on,just try a little bite.
伙计, 别侵犯我的个人空间
Dude,I'm kind of in the zone here.
噢, 为了上帝
Oh,for god's sakes.
真的很好吃
Really tasty.
在这儿要想“戴花环”该怎么做呢?
与上床谐音
So what does a fella have to do to get lei'd around here?
嗯 对 因为我戴了花环
Yeah. Right. 'Cause I'm wearing a lei.
如果你解释了笑话就不好笑了
It isn't funny if you explain the joke.
- 我们走吧
- 别, Barney, 来吧 我玩的很开心
-Let's bail.
-No,barney,come on. I'm having fun.
另外, 再见到这些家伙感觉不错
Plus,it's really great to see all these guys again.
说出一个这派对上你知道的人的名字
Name one person you know at this party.
嗯, 那是忍者
Well,there's ninja,
马屁股 嘿, 马头哪去了?
那家伙是个有趣的人-- 他在哪?
back of horse. Hey,where's front of horse?
That guy's a riot-- where is he?
好吧, 我要走了 但是你要知道
维多利亚秘密派对在一艘游艇上
Okay,I'm leaving. But just know,
that this victoria secret party is on a yacht
谁会在那艘游艇上呢?
"白额黑雁"
And what will be sticking to that yacht?
The "barnacle."
是吗?
Really?
这是你的呢称吗?
That's your nickname now?
- 对, 白额黑雁 - 白额黑雁?
- 就这个
-Yeah,the barnacle. -The barnacle?
-That's it.
白额黑雁, 走啦
Barnacle,out.
玩的开心点, 白额黑雁
Have fun,barnacle.
嗯... 你喜欢Mike吗?
So... do you like mike?
你喜欢Mike吗?
Do you like mike?
当然了 为什么?
Of course I do. Why?
只是看起来不是那样
你不分享你的食物, 你不装扮
It just doesn't seem like it.
You won't share your food,you won't wear a costume.
噢, Lily, 你知道我
我只不是喜欢那些情侣的事情什么的
Oh,lily,you know me.
I'm just not into all that coupley stuff.
好吧, 我知道外面看起来这些事情很傻
Okay,I know that stuff looks dumb from the outside,
但是当你成为其中一员时,就成了世界上最美妙的事情
but it's kind of the greatest thing in the world when you're a part of it.
你如果试一下, 你可能会喜欢上它
If you just gave it a chance,you might like it
你想让我加如什么异教吗?
Are you trying to get me to join a cult?
Robin, Mike喜欢你
Robin,mike likes you.
如果你不做些什么, 你将会失去他
If you don't start meeting him halfway,you're gonna lose him.
什么?
What?
听着, 今天是万圣节
只是这一晚穿上女朋友的服装
Look,it's halloween. Just put on the girlfriend costume for a night.
好吧, 嗯, 我该怎么做
Okay,well,what am i supposed to do,
给他买个巨型泰迪熊吗?
buy him a giant teddy bear or something?
分享你的甜点怎么样?
How about you start by sharing dessert?
- 我可以做到分享甜点
- 很好
-I can share dessert.
-Good.
他更喜欢果仁圣代
He better want the brownie sundae,
但是好, 好, 我完全可以分享
but yeah,yeah,I can totally share.
- Barney? 什么, 你又回来了?
- 你说对了
-barney? What,you're back?
-That's right.
穿着全新的服装
In a totally new costume.
我每个万圣节我都带着一套多余的服装
以防在派对上被女孩踢出局
Every halloween I bring a spare costume,
in case I strike out with the hottest girl at the party.
这样我就可以有第二次机会
给她一个好的第一印象
That way I have a second chance to make a first impression.
你脸怎么啦?
What's with the face?
一边是对你的同情
一边是我想上厕所
It's half you're pathetic,half I have to pee.
那就去厕所啊
So go to the bathroom.
不, 我有大事要做
我不想错过"放浪南瓜"
No,there's a huge line. I don't want to miss the "slutty pumpkin."
那就从楼顶上尿下去
So pee off the roof.
噢, Ted, 在楼顶上尿吧
Ooh, ted, pee off the roof.
哇, 如果我是你我不会这样
有人在这走来走去
Whoa, I wouldn't do that if I were you,
there's people walking down there.
来吧, Ted, 你会听谁的?
Come on, ted, who you gonna listen to?
我, 还是那边的假正经先生?
Me, or mr. Goody-goody over there?
嗯, 无论如何, 你们有大麻吗?
Yeah, whatever, you guys got some weed?
往左挪一点, Marshall Lily, 蹲下
A little to the left, marshall. Lily, squat down.
你们都等着惨败吧
没有一个人的装扮能跟我们相比的!
This is gonna be a slaughter.
None of these other costumes even come close to ourrr...s!
快拍吧
Take the damn picture.
好了
got it.
我还是觉得我们
应该以Sonny和Cher来赢
I still think we should have won as sonny and cher.
也许我该穿那套红衣服
Maybe if I'd worn the red dress.
如果我能回到以前
If I could turn back time.
噢, 哇, 这些圣代看起来来太棒了
我能整个吃下去
oh, wow, this sundae looks so good. I could eat the whole thing.
但, 呃, 我宁愿和你一起
分享这个小小的圣代, Mike
But, um, I would much rather share this small, one-scoop sundae with you, mike.
法式苹果挞? 绝妙的选择, Lily派 谢谢
Apple tart? Excellent choice, lily-pad. Thanks,
Marshall瓜
marshmallow.
嗯, 让我们也开始
Mi... Mi... Mike微波炉
Well, let's dig in, mi... mi... microwave oven.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
这里的每个家伙都和你开了花环玩笑, 是不?
Every guy's used the lei'd line on you tonight, huh?
- 你不会相信
- 我为我的同性道歉
-You wouldn't believe.
-I apologize for my gender.
让我弥补点什么
要喝点什么吗?
Let me make it up to you
make you a drink?
噢 你真是个迷人的恶魔
Oh. You certainly are a charming devil.
我还是个有角的恶魔
与“淫荡”同词
I'm also a "horny" devil.
不
no.
噢, 下地狱吧
Oh, go to hell.
如果你们喜欢提拉米苏
我们找到一家意大利餐厅
You know, if you guys like tiramisu,
we found this little Italian place...
不，你找到的，我跟着你去的
No, you found it. I came with you.
继续
go on.
我刚刚在说, 我们喜欢提拉米苏
I'm just saying, we love tiramisu.
- 我怎么吃也吃不够
- 我们为此疯狂
-I can't get enough of it.
-We're crazy for the stuff.
我疯了, 你也为...
I'm crazy, and you're crazy... ...
- 提拉米苏疯狂
- 对
-for tiramisu.
-Right
“我们”喜欢提拉米苏
We love tiramisu.
我说错了吗？
I wrong saying that?
不, 不, 不 我的意思是
这听起来有点奇怪
No, no, no. I mean,
it just sounds a little bit weird.
是吗?
Doesn't it?
我们喜欢吃提拉米苏?
We love tiramisu?
这不就是两个人一起的活动吗
喜欢提拉米苏?
Isn't really a group activity.
Loving tiramisu?
说说这个意大利餐厅
那里的奶油甜馅煎饼卷怎么样?
So this italian place,
how is their cannoli?
慢点吃, 很饿吗
Easy there, hungry.
是啊, 看起来“我们”都很饿
Yeah, looks like we're both hungry.
- 嘿, 不是Gary Oldman吗? 等等...
- 哪儿?
盖里·欧德曼，出演过
《这个杀手不太冷》《哈里波特》等等
-hey, is that gary oldman? Wait...
-where?
我没看见...
I don't see...
脑袋冻得痛
brain freeze.
- 好吧, 维多利亚秘密派对, 现在
- 不去
-Okay, victoria secret party, right now.
-Nope
我不能忍受自己的好朋友又浪费一个万圣节
Ted, "放浪南瓜"不会出现的
Come on. I can't stand watching my delusional friend waste another precious halloween.
Ted, the "slutty pumpkin" is not coming.
她可能会
She might.
拜托, Barney, 这跟概率没关系,这是信念的问题
come on,Barney, this is not about the odds.
It's about believing.
这个女孩, 她对我来说
代表着一些东西，我不知道 希望
This girl, she... she represents something to me.
I don't know. Hope.
哇 你刚才说的话我一个字也不明白
Wow. I did not understand a word you just said.
在船上的内衣模特!
Lingerie models on a boat!
再见
不 我说再见
See ya.
No. See ya.
想喝点融掉了的吗?
Want to drink the melty part?
你知道吗? 太迟了
You know what? It's getting late.
我想我要离开了
I think I'm gonna take off.
我以为我们会顺着面包屑回我家, Hansel
《糖果屋》中，兄妹俩循着
事先扔下的面包屑回家
Hey. I thought we were gonna follow those bread crumbs back to my place, hansel.
Robin, 我不觉得你喜欢和我在一起
Robin, I don't get the sense you like being with me.
我喜欢和你一起
I like being with you.
没你喜欢一个呆着多
Not as much as you like being alone.
你喜欢... 吃你自己的食物, 睡在自己的床上
做自己的拼字游戏
You like... eatng your own food, sleeping in your own bed, doing your own crosswords.
谁用墨水?
Who uses ink?
抱歉
Sorry.
好吧, 我是有点太自我了
但这并不表示不可行啊
Okay, I'm a bit set in my ways,
that doesn't mean that this won't work.
事实上, 这并不可行
Actually, it kind of does.
等等, 我们要分手吗?
Wait, are we breaking up?
不, “我们”不分手
No, we aren't breaking up.
是“我”要和你分手
I'm breaking up with you.
就在我快失去希望的时候...
And then just when I was about to lose hope...
她花了一年在南极研究企鹅
she spent a year in antarctica studying penguins.
咖啡酒, 纯啤酒...
Kahlua, root beer...
这只企鹅会是"放浪南瓜"吗?
could this penguin be the "slutty pumpkin?"
打扰下 这听起来很疯狂
excuse me. This is going to sound crazy,
但是我4年前在这楼顶上认识了个人
but I met someone up on this roof four years ago,
她喝这样混合的鸡尾酒, 她也喜欢企鹅
and they mixed that cocktail, and-and they loved penguins.
有可能, 是你吗?
By any chance, was that you?
是你吧
It's you.
每个人都觉得我疯了, 但是我...
Everyone thought I was crazy, but I came...
你这个输家
you are such a loser.
拜托, 我是为你回来的, Ted
Come on, I came back for you, ted.
我穿企鹅装来证明你的方式错了
I penguin-suited up to show you the error of your ways.
还拿到了草裙女郎的电话,多确认几遍
And to score hula girl's number. Check and check.
- 不可置信
- 是啊, 确实
-Unbelievable.
-Yes, it is.
噢. 等等 你是那个蹩脚军人
Oh. Wait a minute. You're that lame army guy.
什么? 不, 不, 那是别人,他是出色的飞行员
What? No, no, that's some other guy,
and he was a kick-ass fighter pilot.
我不赶相信我给了你电话
I cannot believe i gave you my number.
对, 嗯, 你给了 谢谢
Yeah, well, you did. Thanks.
对, 嗯, 还给我
Yeah. Well, give it back.
嗯, 呃, 我不这样想
我赚来的, 很公平
Well, uh, I don't think so.
I earned it, fair and square.
我会给你打电话
I'm calling you.
但我绝对不会和你出去
But I'm never gonna go out with you.
但你怎么会知道是我呢?
But how will you know it's me?
我是误导高手
I'm a master of disguise.
很好
nice.
来吧, Ted,维多利亚秘密派对, 就是现在, 走吧
Come on, ted. Victoria secret party, now, let's go.
我要呆在这
I'm staying.
好! 好吧...
Fine! Fine...
你要干什么?
what are you doing?
我用翅膀把你弹开
I'm flippering you off.
噢, 甜心, 我很抱歉
Oh, sweetie, I'm so sorry.
说真的, 这没什么大不了的
Seriously, it's not a big deal.
他想成为我们
He wanted to be a we,
我想成为我自己
and I wanted to be an I.
男人真幼稚
Dudes are such chicks.
伙计们, 我没事
You guys, I'm fine.
先生们小姐们
Ladies and gentlemen,
要公布结果了
the results are in.
今年的最佳装扮奖获得者是...
And the winners of this year's costume contest are...
Lily Aldren装扮的鹦鹉
lily aldren as a parrot,
和Marshall Erikson装扮的同性恋海盗!
and marshall erikson as a gay pirate!
等等, 他说什么?
Wait, what did he say?
噢, 谁在意呢, Marshall? 我们赢了!
Oh, who cares, marshall? We won!
噢, 耶! 等等 同性恋海盗
你从哪听来的?
Oh, yeah!   Wait. Gay pirate
where are you getting that from?
- 兄弟, 你涂眼影了
- 好吧
-Dude, you're wearing eyeliner.
-OK
我只是想说清楚我不是什么同性恋海盗
我一直都和我的鹦鹉有性关系
I just want everybody here to know I'm not a gay pirate.
I have sex with my parrot all the time.
这样说有点问题
That came out wrong.
噢, 耶, 没关系 我们赢了!
Oh, yeah, doesn't matter. We won!
- 我爱你, Marshall瓜
- 我也爱你 Lily派
-I love you, marshmallow.
-I love you, too, lily pad.
你们两个家伙, 让我拍张照
You guys, let me get a picture.
直觉告诉我你在这
I had a feeling I'd find you here.
噢, 嘿 如果你来是为了看Shaggarats
你刚刚错过了第四次演奏的机会
Oh, hey. If you're here for the shaggarats,
you just missed the fourth encore.
我从来不参加组队的运动
I never played any team sports.
我们再说 "我从来不"吗?
因为除了杏仁酒以外什么都没了吗
Are we playing "I never"?
Cause there's nothing left but peach schnapps.
我在高中打网球 知道为什么吗?
I played tennis in high school. You know why?
因为只有我在那
我甚至不能忍受打双打
Because it was just me out there.
I couldn't even stand playing doubles.
我刚被甩了
I just got dumped.
噢, 伙计, 这太糟了
Oh, man, that sucks.
嗯 这没什么
Yeah. It's okay.
我也不是那么迷他
I wasn't that into him.
我的故事
Story of my life.
其他人都沉浸在爱河里做着愚蠢甜蜜的疯事，但是不是我
Everyone else is off falling in love and acting stupid and goofy and sweet and insane, but not me.
为什么我不喜欢这些?
Why don't i want that more?
我希望我想要那些
I want to want that.
我是个怪胎吗?
Am I wired wrong or something?
不是
no.
听着, 你不想和我在一起, 所以
很明显, 你对男人有非同一般的品味
Look, you didn't want to be with me, so,
clearly, you have abysmal taste in men.
但是你怪的刚刚好
but you're wired just fine.
好吧, 如果我是个...冷淡的人呢?
Well, what if I'm just a... a cold person?
今晚Mike愿意为我
做一个彻底的傻瓜, 但是
Tonight mike was willing to look like a complete idiot for me, but
我不愿意做Gretel
为什么我不愿意做Gretel呢?
I couldn't be gretel. Why can't I be gretel?
因为你还没碰到你的Hansel
Because you just haven't met the right hansel yet.
嘿, 有一天，你会遇到一个
让你想做那些白痴事情的人
Hey, one day, you're gonna meet a guy
who's gonna make you want to look like a complete idiot.
真的吗?
真的
Really?
Yeah.
就在某处
He's out there somewhere.
就想那个放浪的南瓜... 南瓜, 南瓜...
Just like the slutty pumpkin... pumpkin, pumpkin...
你怎么做到这些的, Ted?
how do you do this, ted?
你是怎么在这么冷的楼顶上等整晚
仍然相信你的南瓜会出现?
How do you sit out here all night on the roof in the cold,
and still have faith your pumpkin's gonna show up?
嗯, 我喝的很醉
Well, I'm pretty drunk.
听着, 我知道我一生的最爱
穿着南瓜装在……
look, I know that odds are,the love of my life isn't gonna magically walk through that door in a pumpkin costume
零晨2:43走来的几率很低
2:43 in the morning,
但是这看起来
比任何境况都好, 你知道
but this seems as nice a spot as any to just, you know,
坐下来等吧
sit and wait.
--------------------------
西西(*^__^*)
做最好的字幕给亲爱的宝贝